[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which former empire were both Slovenia and Slovakia part of?", "correct_answer": "Austria-Hungary", "incorrect_answers": ["Byzantium", "Ottoman Empire", "Roman Empire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What island is often referred to as the Emerald Isle, the green color being its symbol?", "correct_answer": "Ireland", "incorrect_answers": ["Sicily", "Iceland", "Jamaica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zopf is a type of Swiss bread traditionally consumed on Sunday mornings. What does its name mean?", "correct_answer": "Braid", "incorrect_answers": ["Water", "Shoe", "Sunrise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Christianity is not the main religion in this country.", "correct_answer": "Sri Lanka", "incorrect_answers": ["Armenia", "Uruguay", "East Timor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the town featured in the movie Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "Rock Ridge", "incorrect_answers": ["Brick Ville", "Rock Ville", "Stone Ridge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Italian car brand was founded on June 24, 1910 in Milan. Its badge features a red cross and a serpent devouring a human.", "correct_answer": "Alfa Romeo", "incorrect_answers": ["Lancia", "Fiat", "Ferrari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie, that won best picture at the 45th annual Academy Awards, stars Al Pacino and Marlon Brando?", "correct_answer": "The Godfather", "incorrect_answers": ["Scarecrow", "Serpico", "The Panic In Needle Park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a breed of chicken?", "correct_answer": "Chinese Crested", "incorrect_answers": ["Australorp", "Cubalaya", "Houdan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Bonnie Parker in the 1967 crime movie Bonnie and Clyde?", "correct_answer": "Faye Dunaway", "incorrect_answers": ["Diane Keaton", "Jane Fonda", "Meryl Streep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the title of a 1979 James Bond film.", "correct_answer": "Moonraker", "incorrect_answers": ["Moonspinners", "Moonshadow", "Moondogs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ruled by Saturn, people born under this zodiac sign, are ambitious and practical.", "correct_answer": "Capricorn", "incorrect_answers": ["Pisces", "Sagittarius", "Taurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elliott Coues, William Brewster and Joel Asaph Allen founded this union in September 1883.", "correct_answer": "American Ornithologists Union", "incorrect_answers": ["American Botanists Union", "American Naturalists Union", "American Zoologists Union"]}]